# Tianqi Luan

Web Developer | tluan1@student.gsu.edu | Atlanta, GA | GitHub Link | LinkedIn Profile | Portfolio

### **Summary**

Graduate student with 2+ years of experience in web development and design. Experienced in front-end development with sufficient knowledge in back-end. Proficient in problem solving, data analysis and processing. Strong communication skills that ensure a positive and productive work environment.

#### **Skills**

Language: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, PHP, Python

Framework: React, Node.js, Redux, Bootstrap, Django, Hadoop, PySpark

Tool: Git, Linux, GitLab, GitHub, Slack, Firebase

#### **Experience**

# Front-end Develop Intern | Pure UX | June 2021 - August 2021

- · Front-end developing using React frame work to integrate interactive UIs to website
- · Experience with Redux API development
- · Collaborated with development team to maintain existing code base while creating new functions
- · Leveraged customer feedback to make necessary modifications to increase customer satisfaction

#### Research Assistant | Voice Treatment Lab | October 2021 - Current

- · Develop and test different approaches and tools to predict and improve voice therapy adherence
- · Design and deploy automated analysis algorithm for acoustic data
- · Maintaining mobile acoustic analysis feedback App

# **Projects**

# App.pud.ai

- · Participated in the creation of dashboard, insight and projects pages
- · Designed and developed multiple user-interactive pages based on existing Material UI design
- · Worked with backend Django developers and extracted data from PostgreSQL database
- · Update and push code daily based on design feedback from testing team and real-world user testing with communication done through GitLab

# **COVID-19 Check-In System**

- · A QR-code assigning system which represents the condition of each individuals COVID-19 test result to their unique QR-code and can be checked by building security
- · Potential application includes but not limited to disease screening during pandemic
- Utilize React Native for cross-platform UI rendering, app is compatible with IOS, Android and web browsers like Google Chrome
- · Firebase database establish for all user data and COVID-19 related information

#### **Education**

· Master of Computer Science | 2019-2022 | Georgia State University, Atlanta, GA